{
    "data": [
        {
            "id": 18,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Maintain Files & Folders",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 88,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for operating systems",
                                "answer": "Microsoft Windows, Linux, Ubuntu, Mac OS",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 89,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the common features of an operating system",
                                "answer": "Memory management, File handling, Security management, Disk space management, Task management",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 90,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of file attributes",
                                "answer": "System, Read only, Hidden, Archive",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 91,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to manage files in an Operating System",
                                "answer": "By grouping them inside the folders.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 92,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the different between file and folder",
                                "answer": "File is a single document, Folder can hold collection of files/documents.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 93,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of open-source software",
                                "answer": "Open-source softwares are freely available to use and it's source (source code) is freely available for users.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 94,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of closed-source software",
                                "answer": "Closed-sourced software which has an owner, without a permission it does not available freely.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 95,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of file compression",
                                "answer": "Reduce the file size by using a file compression software.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 96,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for file compression softwares",
                                "answer": "WinZip, WinRAR, 7zip",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 97,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of system restore",
                                "answer": "System Restore is a feature in Microsoft Windows that allows the user to revert their computer's state to that of a previous point in time, which can be used to recover from system malfunctions or other problems.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 98,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of computer virus",
                                "answer": "It is a specific computer program which makes harmful activities or malfunctioning in a computer.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 99,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is anti-virus software/virus guard",
                                "answer": "It is a software which created to protect computer from harmful programs.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 100,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for ant-virus softwares",
                                "answer": "Avast, Kaspersky, Avira, AVG, BitDefender, Norton",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 101,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to recognize virus infection in a computer",
                                "answer": "Slow down computer, Unexpected computer restarting, Malfunctioning softwares, Unexpected hard disk filling, CPU over heating, System crashes",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 102,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to avoid from computer viruses",
                                "answer": "Use proper anti-virus software and make sure to update it, Avoid from unsure pen drive or software installing, Avoid from clicking spam emails or spam links, Make sure to install legitimate softwares rather than installing pirate or cracked softwares, Make sure to backup your important data",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 19,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Perform Word Processing",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 103,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is word processing",
                                "answer": "Creating documents or letters by using a word processing software",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 104,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of word processor",
                                "answer": "Word processor is a software which allows to create, edit, print documents.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 105,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the commonly use word processing softwares",
                                "answer": "Microsoft Word, OpenOffice Writer, Google Docs, LibreOffice Writer",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 106,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the features of word processing software",
                                "answer": "Creating, editing, saving and printing documents, Copying, pasting, moving and deleting text within a document, Formatting text, such as font type, bolding, underlining or italicizing, Creating and editing tables, Inserting elements from other software, such as illustrations or photographs",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 107,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the best way to create 100 letters with different names and addresses in an efficiently",
                                "answer": "Creating a mail merge document and making copies from it.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 108,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the way of placing an image or a clip art behind the text without making interrupt",
                                "answer": "Placing the image as watermark image.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 109,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of letter cases in MS Word",
                                "answer": "Lower case, Upper case, Sentence case, Toggle case",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 110,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of page orientations modes in MS Word",
                                "answer": "Portrait, Landscape",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 111,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to style a document title in MS Word",
                                "answer": "By creating it as WordArt.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 112,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to create dummy text in word document",
                                "answer": "By typing '=Rand()'",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 20,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Maintain Files & Folders",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 113,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for operating systems",
                                "answer": "Microsoft Windows, Linux, Ubuntu, Mac OS",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 114,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the common features of an operating system",
                                "answer": "Memory management, File handling, Security management, Disk space management, Task management",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 115,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of file attributes",
                                "answer": "System, Read only, Hidden, Archive",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 116,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to manage files in an Operating System",
                                "answer": "By grouping them inside the folders.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 117,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the different between file and folder",
                                "answer": "File is a single document, Folder can hold collection of files/documents.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 118,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of open-source software",
                                "answer": "Open-source softwares are freely available to use and it's source (source code) is freely available for users.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 119,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of closed-source software",
                                "answer": "Closed-sourced software which has an owner, without a permission it does not available freely.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 120,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of file compression",
                                "answer": "Reduce the file size by using a file compression software.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 121,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for file compression softwares",
                                "answer": "WinZip, WinRAR, 7zip",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 122,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of system restore",
                                "answer": "System Restore is a feature in Microsoft Windows that allows the user to revert their computer's state to that of a previous point in time, which can be used to recover from system malfunctions or other problems.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 123,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of computer virus",
                                "answer": "It is a specific computer program which makes harmful activities or malfunctioning in a computer.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 124,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is anti-virus software/virus guard",
                                "answer": "It is a software which created to protect computer from harmful programs.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 125,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for ant-virus softwares",
                                "answer": "Avast, Kaspersky, Avira, AVG, BitDefender, Norton",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 126,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to recognize virus infection in a computer",
                                "answer": "Slow down computer, Unexpected computer restarting, Malfunctioning softwares, Unexpected hard disk filling, CPU over heating, System crashes",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 127,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to avoid from computer viruses",
                                "answer": "Use proper anti-virus software and make sure to update it, Avoid from unsure pen drive or software installing, Avoid from clicking spam emails or spam links, Make sure to install legitimate softwares rather than installing pirate or cracked softwares, Make sure to backup your important data",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 21,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Perform Word Processing",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 128,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is word processing",
                                "answer": "Creating documents or letters by using a word processing software",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 129,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of word processor",
                                "answer": "Word processor is a software which allows to create, edit, print documents.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 130,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the commonly use word processing softwares",
                                "answer": "Microsoft Word, OpenOffice Writer, Google Docs, LibreOffice Writer",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 131,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the features of word processing software",
                                "answer": "Creating, editing, saving and printing documents, Copying, pasting, moving and deleting text within a document, Formatting text, such as font type, bolding, underlining or italicizing, Creating and editing tables, Inserting elements from other software, such as illustrations or photographs",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 132,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the best way to create 100 letters with different names and addresses in an efficiently",
                                "answer": "Creating a mail merge document and making copies from it.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 133,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the way of placing an image or a clip art behind the text without making interrupt",
                                "answer": "Placing the image as watermark image.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 134,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of letter cases in MS Word",
                                "answer": "Lower case, Upper case, Sentence case, Toggle case",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 135,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of page orientations modes in MS Word",
                                "answer": "Portrait, Landscape",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 136,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to style a document title in MS Word",
                                "answer": "By creating it as WordArt.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 137,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to create dummy text in word document",
                                "answer": "By typing '=Rand()'",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 22,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Maintain Files & Folders",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 138,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for operating systems",
                                "answer": "Microsoft Windows, Linux, Ubuntu, Mac OS",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 139,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the common features of an operating system",
                                "answer": "Memory management, File handling, Security management, Disk space management, Task management",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 140,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of file attributes",
                                "answer": "System, Read only, Hidden, Archive",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 141,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to manage files in an Operating System",
                                "answer": "By grouping them inside the folders.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 142,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the different between file and folder",
                                "answer": "File is a single document, Folder can hold collection of files/documents.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 143,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of open-source software",
                                "answer": "Open-source softwares are freely available to use and it's source (source code) is freely available for users.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 144,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of closed-source software",
                                "answer": "Closed-sourced software which has an owner, without a permission it does not available freely.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 145,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of file compression",
                                "answer": "Reduce the file size by using a file compression software.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 146,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for file compression softwares",
                                "answer": "WinZip, WinRAR, 7zip",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 147,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of system restore",
                                "answer": "System Restore is a feature in Microsoft Windows that allows the user to revert their computer's state to that of a previous point in time, which can be used to recover from system malfunctions or other problems.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 148,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of computer virus",
                                "answer": "It is a specific computer program which makes harmful activities or malfunctioning in a computer.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 149,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is anti-virus software/virus guard",
                                "answer": "It is a software which created to protect computer from harmful programs.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 150,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for ant-virus softwares",
                                "answer": "Avast, Kaspersky, Avira, AVG, BitDefender, Norton",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 151,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to recognize virus infection in a computer",
                                "answer": "Slow down computer, Unexpected computer restarting, Malfunctioning softwares, Unexpected hard disk filling, CPU over heating, System crashes",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 152,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to avoid from computer viruses",
                                "answer": "Use proper anti-virus software and make sure to update it, Avoid from unsure pen drive or software installing, Avoid from clicking spam emails or spam links, Make sure to install legitimate softwares rather than installing pirate or cracked softwares, Make sure to backup your important data",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 23,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Perform Word Processing",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 153,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is word processing",
                                "answer": "Creating documents or letters by using a word processing software",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 154,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of word processor",
                                "answer": "Word processor is a software which allows to create, edit, print documents.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 155,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the commonly use word processing softwares",
                                "answer": "Microsoft Word, OpenOffice Writer, Google Docs, LibreOffice Writer",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 156,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the features of word processing software",
                                "answer": "Creating, editing, saving and printing documents, Copying, pasting, moving and deleting text within a document, Formatting text, such as font type, bolding, underlining or italicizing, Creating and editing tables, Inserting elements from other software, such as illustrations or photographs",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 157,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the best way to create 100 letters with different names and addresses in an efficiently",
                                "answer": "Creating a mail merge document and making copies from it.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 158,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the way of placing an image or a clip art behind the text without making interrupt",
                                "answer": "Placing the image as watermark image.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 159,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of letter cases in MS Word",
                                "answer": "Lower case, Upper case, Sentence case, Toggle case",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 160,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of page orientations modes in MS Word",
                                "answer": "Portrait, Landscape",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 161,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to style a document title in MS Word",
                                "answer": "By creating it as WordArt.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 162,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to create dummy text in word document",
                                "answer": "By typing '=Rand()'",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 24,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Prepare Spreadsheet",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 163,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is Microsoft Excel",
                                "answer": "Microsoft Excel is said to be a spreadsheet application or an electronic worksheet that is helpful for storing, analyzing data, manipulating data, and organizing reports.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 164,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Provide the different types of data formats available in Excel",
                                "answer": "Accounting, Date, Percentage, Number, and Text are the different data formats available in Excel.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 165,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Define Format Painter",
                                "answer": "If you want to copy the format of a cell, text, image etc and apply on another text, the Format painter is used.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 166,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Define cells in Excel",
                                "answer": "The place where we store the data is called a cell.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 167,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "List out the charts available in MS Excel",
                                "answer": "Pie, Bar, Scatter, Line are some of the available charts in MS Excel, which is useful to provide graphical representation of a report/analysis.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 168,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the function used to get the total of columns and rows in Excel",
                                "answer": "To get the total of columns and rows in Excel, use the function 'SUM'.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 169,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the use of 'IF' function in Excel",
                                "answer": "To verify whether the conditions are true or false, the function 'IF' is used in Excel.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 170,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Give the advantage of Look Up function in Excel",
                                "answer": "To return a value for array, you can use the function Look Up.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 171,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Provide the shortcut for find and replace",
                                "answer": "Ctrl+F is the shortcut key to open the find tab and Ctrl+H is the shortcut to open find and replace tab.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 172,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "To perform auto-sum on the rows and columns, what is the shortcut",
                                "answer": "ALT=' is the shortcut to perform auto-sum on the rows and columns.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 25,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Prepare Presentations",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 173,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Which power point view works best for adding slide transition",
                                "answer": "Slide sorter view",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 174,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Which option can be used to set custom timings for slides in a presentation",
                                "answer": "Rehearsal",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 175,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What PowerPoint feature will you use to apply motion effects to different objects of a slide",
                                "answer": "Animation Scheme",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 176,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the difference between Slide Design and Auto Content Wizard",
                                "answer": "Slide Design does not provide sample content but Auto Content Wizard provides sample content too.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 177,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "In which menu can you find features like Slide Design, Slide Layout etc.",
                                "answer": "Format Menu",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 178,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Which menu provides you options like Animation Scheme, custom Animation, Slide Transition",
                                "answer": "Slide Show Menu",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 179,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the short cut key to insert a new slide in current presentation",
                                "answer": "Ctrl+M",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 180,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the best way to create another copy of a slide",
                                "answer": "From Insert Menu choose Duplicate Slide.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 181,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What happens if you edited an image inserted in PowerPoint",
                                "answer": "The original file that was inserted is not changed.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 182,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "In Microsoft PowerPoint, what are the two kinds of sound effects files that can be added to the presentation",
                                "answer": ".wave file, .mid file",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 183,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is a motion path",
                                "answer": "A method of moving items on a slide.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 184,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is a slide-title master pair",
                                "answer": "A slide master and title master for a specific design template.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 185,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the view that displays the slides on a presentation as miniature representations of the slides",
                                "answer": "Slide sorter view",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 186,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the PowerPoint view that displays only text",
                                "answer": "Outline view",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 187,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the shortcut key can be used to view slide show",
                                "answer": "F5",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 26,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Maintain Databases",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 188,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is a database",
                                "answer": "A database is an organized collection of data, generally stored and accessed electronically from a computer system.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 189,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is DBMS (Database Management System)",
                                "answer": "A database management system (DBMS) is software for creating and managing databases.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 190,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is primary key",
                                "answer": "Primary key is a unique identifier of a table.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 191,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is foreign key",
                                "answer": "Foreign key is a primary key of another table which helps to make relationships between tables.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 192,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is an entity",
                                "answer": "An entity is something that exists separately from other things and has a clear identity.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 193,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is an attribute",
                                "answer": "An attribute is a characteristic of an entity.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 194,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the three basic relationship types use in DBMS",
                                "answer": "one-to-one, one-to-many, many-to-many",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 195,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is ERD (Entity Relationship Diagram)",
                                "answer": "Diagram for use in database design.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 196,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is SQL stands for",
                                "answer": "Structured Query Language",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 197,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for DBMS",
                                "answer": "Microsoft Access, Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, Oracle",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 27,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Perform Internet and Email Operations",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 198,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is HTML stands for",
                                "answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 199,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is static web page",
                                "answer": "A static Web page is a page that is built using HTML.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 200,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is dynamic web page",
                                "answer": "A dynamic web page is a web page that displays different content each time it's viewed.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 201,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are languages use to create dynamic web pages",
                                "answer": "JavaScript, DHTML, VBScript",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 202,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is W3C stands for",
                                "answer": "World Wide Web Consortium.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 203,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How the W3C relate with the WWW (World Wide Web)",
                                "answer": "The World Wide Web Consortium is the main international standards organization for the World Wide Web.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 204,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is CSS stands for",
                                "answer": "Cascading Style Sheets.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 205,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is hyperlink",
                                "answer": "A link from a hypertext document to another location.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 206,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the rendering tool/software of HTML",
                                "answer": "Web browser/ Web Client",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 207,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is a cookie in website",
                                "answer": "A small text file created by a website that is stored in the user's data.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 208,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is a website",
                                "answer": "A website is a collection of publicly accessible, interlinked Web pages.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 209,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is an attachment",
                                "answer": "An attachment, or email attachment, is a file sent with an email message.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 210,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the Cc and Bcc in email",
                                "answer": "Cc - Carbon Copy, Bcc - Blind Carbon Copy",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 211,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How the Cc and Bcc differentiate?",
                                "answer": "The difference between Cc and Bcc is that carbon copy (CC) recipients are visible to all other recipients whereas those who are BCCed are not visible to anyone.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 212,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is search engine",
                                "answer": "A web search engine is a web application that is designed to search for information on the World Wide Web.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 28,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Install and Configure Operating System",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 213,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the components of a computer system",
                                "answer": "Hardware, Software, Liveware, Firmware",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 214,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the components of CPU",
                                "answer": "ALU (Arithmetic logic unit), CU (Control unit), Registers",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 215,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is FSB (Front Side Bus)",
                                "answer": "The Front Side Bus connects the CPU to main memory.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 216,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is BSB (Back Side Bus)",
                                "answer": "It connects the CPU to a Level 2 cache.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 217,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the three types of cashe memories",
                                "answer": "Level 1, Level 2, Level 3",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 218,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is primary memory in computer",
                                "answer": "RAM (Main Memory), ROM",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 219,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is a volatile memory",
                                "answer": "RAM (Random Access Memory)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 220,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is a non-volatile memory",
                                "answer": "ROM (Read Only Memory)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 221,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the different between volatile and non-volatile",
                                "answer": "Volatile Memory is a type of memory in which data contained in the memory is lost whenever the power is turned off. Non-volatile memory as once the user turns off your computer then content remains intact and will not get lost.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 222,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is secondary memory in computer",
                                "answer": "Hard disk, Optical drives (CD/DVD-ROM), Flash drives (Pen drive)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 223,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the port which supports multiple devices",
                                "answer": "USB port",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 224,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is hot-swappable",
                                "answer": "Hot-swappable means that you can plug in or remove a device without first shutting down your computer.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 225,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is plug and play",
                                "answer": "Computer will recognize it as soon as it is installed.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 226,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the four classifications of computers",
                                "answer": "Supercomputer, Mainframe Computer, Minicomputer, Microcomputer",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 227,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the types of operating systems",
                                "answer": "Real time OS, Single user-single task OS, Single user-multi task OS, Multi user-multi task OS",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 228,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is BIOS (Basic Input/Output System)",
                                "answer": "The built-in program which controls the primary functions of a computer.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 29,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Installation and Troubleshooting of LAN",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 229,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is computer a network",
                                "answer": "A computer network is a set of computers connected together for the purpose of sharing resources.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 230,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is network topology",
                                "answer": "Network topology refers to the physical or logical layout of a network.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 231,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the basic network topologies",
                                "answer": "Bus, Star, Ring, Mesh",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 232,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the hybrid topology",
                                "answer": "Hybrid topology is an interconnection of two or more basic network topologies.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 233,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the example for Hybrid topology",
                                "answer": "Tree topology",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 234,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the basic data transmission/communication modes",
                                "answer": "Simplex, Half-duplex, Full-duplex",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 235,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the data transmission/communication modes among network devices",
                                "answer": "Unicast, Multicast, Broadcast",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 236,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the two types of network architectures",
                                "answer": "Client-server architecture, Peer-to-peer architecture",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 237,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is protocol",
                                "answer": "A protocol is a set of rules that governs the communications between computers on a network.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 238,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is IP stands for",
                                "answer": "Internet Protocol",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 239,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the use of IP address",
                                "answer": "An IP address, or simply an \"IP,\" is a unique address that identifies a device on the Internet or a local network.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 240,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the different between IP address and MAC (Media Access Control) address",
                                "answer": "IP address is a logical address which can be changed. MAC address is a physical address which cannot be changed.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 241,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the different types of network",
                                "answer": "PAN(Personal Area Network), LAN (Local Area Network), MAN(Metropolitan Area Network), WAN(Wide Area Network)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 242,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the basic protocols govern the network / internet",
                                "answer": "TCP (Transmission Control Protocol), IP (Internet Protocol)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 243,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is bandwidth",
                                "answer": "Maximum data transfer rate of a network or Internet connection.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 244,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the unguided/unbound media",
                                "answer": "Radio wave, Micro wave, Infrared",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 245,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the guided/bound media",
                                "answer": "Coaxial, Twisted-Pair, Fiber optics",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 246,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the three basic requirements for data communication",
                                "answer": "Sender, Medium, Receiver",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 247,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the two types of conceptual models use in networking",
                                "answer": "OSI (Open System Interconnection) model, TCP/IP model",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 248,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Which are the layers of OSI model can be directly interacted with user",
                                "answer": "Application Layer (Layer 7) – User Interfaces, Physical Layer (Layer 1) – Network cables and hubs",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 249,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is domain name",
                                "answer": "A domain name is simply a human readable form of an IP address.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 250,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the use of DNS (Domain Name System)",
                                "answer": "Domain name to IP mapping is done by DNS",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 251,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the use of DHCP (Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol)",
                                "answer": "DHCP is a protocol for assigning dynamic IP addresses to devices on a network.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 252,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the two types of IP addresses",
                                "answer": "Static IP (Permanent IP), Dynamic IP (Temporary IP)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 253,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the use of 'ipconfig' command in Windows",
                                "answer": "ipconfig' allows you to get the IP address information of a Windows computer.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 254,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the use of 'ping' command",
                                "answer": "ping' allows a user to verify that a particular IP address exists and can accept requests.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 30,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Develop Graphics for Online / Print Media",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 255,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is a pixel",
                                "answer": "Smallest unit of the digital image/display.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 256,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is pixel resolution",
                                "answer": "Total number of pixels of a digital image/display.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 257,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "How to measure resolution",
                                "answer": "Pixel per inch (ppi)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 258,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is vector graphics",
                                "answer": "Points and paths based graphics.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 259,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is raster graphic",
                                "answer": "Pixel based graphics.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 260,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the primary/additive colors",
                                "answer": "Red, Green, Blue",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 261,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the secondary/subtractive/four/process colors",
                                "answer": "Cyan, Magenta, Yellow, Black",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 262,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the application of primary colors",
                                "answer": "Digital displays / images.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 263,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the application of secondary colors",
                                "answer": "Printing purposes.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 264,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the suitable image file types for web",
                                "answer": "jpeg, png, gif",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 265,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the popular vector graphic softwares",
                                "answer": "Adobe Illustrator, Corel Draw",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 266,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the popular raster graphic softwares",
                                "answer": "Adobe Photoshop, GIMP",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 31,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Design Web Pages",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 267,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the relationship between HTML and CSS",
                                "answer": "CSS is used to style the HTML pages.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 268,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Which tag is used to create hyperlink",
                                "answer": "Anchor tag ('a' tag)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 269,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of empty tag",
                                "answer": "Empty tags does not contain attributes inside the tag.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 270,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of self-closing tag",
                                "answer": "Self-closing tag does not include closing tag.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 271,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the current version of HTML",
                                "answer": "Version 5",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 272,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the current version of CSS",
                                "answer": "Version 3",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 273,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of CSS framework",
                                "answer": "It is a complete package which helps to decorate HTML pages easily.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 274,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for CSS frameworks",
                                "answer": "Bootstrap, Foundation, Skeleton, Tailwind",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 275,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the tags that can be used to design the layout of a web page",
                                "answer": "div' Tag, 'table' Tag",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 276,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "Who is the responsible person for manage a website in an organization",
                                "answer": "Web Administrator",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 277,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the advantage of dynamic web page",
                                "answer": "Dynamic web pages can generate different content according to the situation, user or session.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 278,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the three types of including CSS to a web page",
                                "answer": "Inline, Internal, External",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 279,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the tag that can be used to create HTML animations",
                                "answer": "marquee' tag",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 280,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for web programming languages",
                                "answer": "PHP, ASP.NET, JSP, JavaScript",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 281,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the requirements for publish a website",
                                "answer": "Hosting service, Domain name",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 282,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the importance of a domain name",
                                "answer": "Domain name can be used as an unique identifier for a particular website.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 283,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "When you upload your website to a hosting server, how to define your home page",
                                "answer": "The home page should be rename as 'index.html'",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 32,
            "attributes": {
                "name": "Develop Basic Software Solution",
                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                "questions": {
                    "data": [
                        {
                            "id": 284,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the stages/phases of SDLS (System Development Life Cycle)",
                                "answer": "Planning, Analysis, Design, Implementation, Testing, Maintenance",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 285,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are facts finding methods using in analysis phase",
                                "answer": "Sampling of existing documentation, Research and Site visits, Observation of the work environment, Questionnaires, Interviews, Prototyping, Joint requirements planning",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 286,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the output of analysis phase in SDLC",
                                "answer": "SRS (Software Requirements Specification) Document.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 287,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the main two types of designing",
                                "answer": "Logical design, Physical design",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 288,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the different between logical and physical design",
                                "answer": "Logical design represent the data flow of the system, physical design represent the data storing (database) of the system.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 289,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is DFD stands for",
                                "answer": "Data Flow Diagram.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 290,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the using of DFD",
                                "answer": "To represent the data flow of the system.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 291,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the two types of programming approaches",
                                "answer": "Functional programming, Object oriented programming (OOP)",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 292,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the three types of control structures/control construct",
                                "answer": "Sequential, Selection/Conditional, Looping/Iteration/Repeating",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 293,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the commonly use programming languages",
                                "answer": "Java, Python, PHP, JavaScript, Visual Basic, C#",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 294,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the different between compiler and interpreter",
                                "answer": "Compiler converts the whole program in one goes on the other hand. Interpreter converts the program by taking a single line at a time.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 295,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the different between high level languages and low level languages",
                                "answer": "Low level language is machine readable form of program. High level language will be in human readable form.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 296,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for high level programming languages",
                                "answer": "Java, Python, PHP, JavaScript, Visual Basic, C#",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 297,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the examples for low level programming languages",
                                "answer": "Machine code, Assembly language",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 298,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the term called \"bug\" in programming",
                                "answer": "A software bug is an error, flaw, failure or fault in a computer program.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 299,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of debug",
                                "answer": "The process of identifying and removing errors from computer hardware or software.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 300,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of \"Source code\"",
                                "answer": "Source code is the set of instructions and statements written by a programmer using a computer programming language.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 301,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What are the main types of software testing methods",
                                "answer": "Black box testing, White box testing, Gray box testing",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 302,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of unit testing",
                                "answer": "Testing the smallest part of individual unit / component of the system.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 303,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of integration testing",
                                "answer": "Program units are combined and testing as groups.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 304,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of system testing",
                                "answer": "System testing is done after integration testing, testing the system as a whole.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 305,
                            "attributes": {
                                "question": "What is the meaning of acceptance testing",
                                "answer": "Last phase of the software testing process. A system is tested for acceptability.",
                                "createdAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "updatedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22",
                                "publishedAt": "2025-09-01 13:51:22"
                            }
                        }
                    ]
                }
            }
        }
    ]
}
